♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who
positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Good evening. Coming up,
a major Hollywood movie
is set to film in Quahog.
But first,
whoever recorded me
cursing at
that freeway off-ramp veteran,
please don't post that,
all right, seriously.
We all have bad days.
Our top story:
the latest Brad Pitt film
will be shot
right here in Quahog.
Pitt will play
former New Jersey governor
Chris Christie.
Brad Pitt is playing
Chris Christie?!
It should be a fat guy
playing that role!
Chris Christie didn't eat
10,000 Jersey Mike's subs
just to be played
by a Hollywood pretty boy.
That's offensive, and I,
for one, will not stand for it.
Although that's mostly
due to cardiovascular disease.
I got to sit down.
Peter, you know, you've
actually got a valid point.
Oh, boy. Here comes the soapbox.
It's shameful Hollywood would
pass over the many talented
plus-sized actors who are
much more deserving of the role.
-Name two.
-Jonah Hill?
-He's thin now.
-Uh, Fat Albert?
-Not real.
-James Corden?
He's been canceled
for sending eggs back.
Well, it's just another example
of Hollywood's history
of exclusionary casting,
-whitewashing and thin-washing.
-Exactly.
Like Mike Myers playing
an Indian man in The Love Guru.
-[giggles]
-Or Marlon and Shawn Wayans
-playing White Chicks.
-[giggles]
Or Mickey Rooney playing
an offensive stereotype
of an Asian man
in Breakfast at Tiffany's.
I don't know that movie,
but I like breakfast.
Oh, come on, you two.
You're really offended that
one of the biggest movie stars
on the planet is coming to
our crap town to shoot a movie?
I mean, Brad Pitt could put it
anywhere,
-with any of us.
-Facts.
I mean, when was the last time
a celebrity visited Quahog?
-Uh, Jared Fogle.
-Who?
The Subway Guy. Remember?
He was here
for a public appearance.
Took a shine to Chris
for some reason.
Took him camping.
Had these weird candies
he'd only let Chris eat.
How come I don't remember
any of this?
Ah, too many video games,
buddy.
They're rotting your brains.
Get your hands off me, Jared!
You're really gonna complain
about Brad Pitt?
Who cares what role
he's playing?!
Well, that's easy
for you to say, Lois.
Women have no idea
what it's like for us men,
being held up to
impossible standards of beauty
in the media.
Ooh, Jennifer Lawrence has
a new movie.
Eh! Too old. Next.
Peter, I think
you're right to protest.
-I'll even join you.
-Thanks, Brian.
Sometimes you just got
to stand up for what's right.
That's why I stood up
to Kanye West.
Dinosaurs were created
by the Illuminati.
The government hides secrets
in SpaghettiOs.
And Hitler would've
won Wimbledon
if he played tennis, bro.
Sir, sir, sir.
We do not wear shoes
in this house.
Thank you. Now please
continue about Wimbledon.
[chanting]
Overweight is overdue!
Wow, I'm impressed, Peter.
Yeah, it's going great.
News trucks even showed up
to cover it.
I-I think... I think those
are just food trucks.
Come on, you know you want some.
Hi, fellas.
Oh, hey. Thanks for coming out
to support us.
"Dangerous Curves Ahead."
-Oh...
-[laughs] Right?
[laughs]
Oh, that is good.
[laughing]
You get it.
[laughs]
That... that is clever.
Am I right?
[laughter]
That, that's good.
That's good.
-Isn't it, though? [laughs]
-Yeah, yeah.
[whispers] Brian, can you
explain that shirt to me later?
Protesters were on hand today
at the set of
the new Chris Christie biopic
being filmed in Quahog.
They were protesting the casting
of Hollywood superstar Brad Pitt
in the lead role
and not a person of heft.
Well, Peter, I'm just glad
you're on the news
for something other than sitting
on a hamster at a school event.
[clamoring]
Hey, they said they weren't
gonna put that!
[doorbell rings]
Mr. Griffin, hi.
I'm Josh Universal
from the movie.
I'm taking a break
from my horrific cocaine habit
to ask you
to sit down with our producers
for a "listening session"
to hear your concerns.
And, on an unrelated note,
can I use your bathroom,
and does anyone have
a rolled-up bill?
Oh, of course. I got
a special five just for that.
[sniffs] All right, let's get
zapped and go see a play!
♪ ♪
Hmm. That's odd.
Mr. Griffin, thank you
for meeting with us.
Have a seat.
Not on my lap!
Sorry. [chuckles]
I'm a little nervous.
Peter Griffin,
please meet Brad Pitt.
♪ ♪
[gasps]
George Clooney's boyfriend?
No, no. A few years ago,
he was cast in a marriage.
Mr. Griffin,
we've asked you here
because we understand
you have an issue
with Brad playing the lead role
in our movie.
We want to make sure we hear
and ignore all your concerns.
Look, I know Brad Pitt is
a big star and all,
but he's playing Chris Christie,
who's a fat guy.
It seems unfair that
the role didn't go to a fat guy.
It only makes sense.
Don't you think
we should cast the best actor,
letting them interpret the role,
rather than depending
on physical traits?
Not if you're taking the role
away from a fat guy.
But, Mr. Griffin, Brad Pitt is
a highly skilled actor
who's won an Oscar and lots
of garbage Golden Globes.
You're not hearing my concerns.
You don't know
the challenges fat guys face.
What it's like
to have to rock multiple times
to get off the couch,
or how it feels to have to poke
a new hole in your belt
with a nail,
only to realize
the end no longer
tucks into the little loop,
or the shame
of getting thrown out
of a strip club for touching.
That last thing doesn't seem
like a weight issue.
You sound just like the judge!
Look, the casting of this movie
is offensive to fat people,
and I won't rest
until it gets shut down.
Mr. Griffin, look,
what if we made you our
"official fat guy consultant"?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Yes! What if I told you
we'll give you a P.A. who will
get you anything you want?
Deal. 20 Happy Meals, please.
He's actually Judd Apatow's
nephew Zack.
You can't tell him what to do.
In fact, you work for him.
I want you to get me this thing,
and I can't remember
what it is or where I saw it.
Wow, I'm gonna learn so much
from his last name.
[fighting and gunfire on TV]
The new season of White Lotus
is weird.
Griffins, you are looking at
the Chris Christie movie's
official fat guy consultant.
Boy, that's a garbage title
if I ever heard one.
What? Wait a minute,
so instead of demanding
they cast a plus-sized actor,
you caved
when they offered you
a meaningless title?
-What about
everything you fought for?
-Don't you see, Brian?
Now I can work the system
from the inside with dignity.
-[phone rings]
-Yes, Mr. Apatow's nephew?
[deflated]
Yes, Mr. Apatow's nephew.
[crying]
What does a fat guy consultant
even do?
I'm the personal
weight-gain coach for Brad Pitt.
Wou-Would we get to meet him?
Sure. My job is
to teach him how to think,
eat and live like a fat guy.
So, just like that,
you're giving up?
Brian, I'm a fat guy.
I got all fired up
about something,
and now I'm tired
and I'd like some custard.
Guys, I'd like you to meet
my new friend Brad Pitt.
-Oh, my God!
-Whoa, nice to meet you.
-Who's this now?
-He's a very famous actor.
He's like
the white Morris Chestnut.
-Oh, damn!
-Wow!
I can't believe I'm sitting here
with Brad Pitt.
I've got so many questions.
Like, what are the other rules
of Fight Club?
Well, the first rule is--
No, I'm clear on the first rule.
And I know the second rule is
just repeating the first.
But there's got to be
loads more.
Like, I got to think
"no sack attacks" is on there.
Hey, Brad.
Any chance I could get
Jennifer Aniston's number
from you?
I know she's got to be
a nightmare,
but she keeps it
so freakin' tight.
Okay, enough small talk.
Let's do
what I brought him here for:
to break the Internet
with a group
-head-smushed-together selfie.
-[phone beeps]
[camera clicks]
Kevin Spacey?
Get out of here.
You're not allowed to be
in head-smushed-together photos
after what you did.
Not guilty
on all British counts.
[chuckles] Oh, that rascal.
[knocking]
Hi, you must be Peter's wife.
I'm Brad.
♪ ♪
Oh, I know who you are.
I'm-- [screams]
Hi, I'm-- [screams]
Stewart. Charmed.
I know you dump people
when they're 40,
but that still gives us
39 good years.
Pleased to meet you, Mr. Pitt.
Um, when you did
that movie Snatch,
did you know
that also means something else?
Because it very much does.
That's a sticky handshake
you got there, Chris.
Peter, I was wondering
if I could spend some time
with you and your family,
observing how you live
and how you eat,
to prepare for the role.
Sure, I'd be glad to help.
Wow, I ain't had a celebrity
ask me for a favor
since Jeremy Renner asked me
to shovel out his driveway.
-[engine idling]
-Uh, Jeremy, in light of
recent events, uh...
could ol' Pete borrow your skis?
Okay, Brad, I'm gonna teach you
to be a fat guy.
For starters,
this is where we eat.
Um, excuse me, Mr. Pitt,
but would you mind
if I FaceTime my friends
with you here?
Oh, my God, they'll go crazy!
Sure, Meg, it'd be my pleasure.
-[squeals]
-[FaceTime app ringing]
Oh, boy.
Oh, this-this is sad.
Oh, this-this is just... Oh...
Why don't I just take this,
dear.
-[ringing stops]
-[phone beeps]
Okay, Brad, now,
another fat guy rule is that
when you're out at restaurants,
always act like
you're on the fence
about dessert.
So, folks, we thinking dessert?
Seriously? You must be joking.
I cannot move.
No, sir. No way.
Absolutely stuffed to the gills.
Gonna have to take a rain check.
Although... No, no,
I can't even suggest it.
We are done. Done-a-roo.
Check, please.
Although... just thinking,
I don't know when
we'll be back here.
I read about
the award-winning pastry chef--
Wait, what am I saying? No! No.
Stop me, please,
someone, please.
Bring the check now.
Okay, you know what, we'll get
one order and we'll all share.
One dessert, one dish,
five spoons.
Whoever wants can have some.
One plate. One of everything.
My plate.
One spoon. No share.
Now, Brad, if you're gonna
play a fat guy on camera,
you got to learn
how to do the rope swing.
Okay, let me show you
how it's done.
[groans]
900,000 views.
-I'm learning so much.
-That's great.
Hey, can you click
on a porn site for me?
Otherwise I got to
peck it with my nose
like a tic-tac-toe chicken.
Here you go.
Thanks so much, Mrs. Griffin.
I love a home-cooked meal.
Well, we are
so happy to have you.
-How's Shiloh?
-Who?
-How's Maddox?
-How's Zahara?
-Who?
-How's Pax?
-How's Vivienne?
-Who?
-How's Knox?
Ignore her,
she can be so annoying.
Sometimes I wish
I had a private plane
just so I could choke her on it.
Hey, can I get you anything?
Another pork-n-Cheetos sandwich
or a buffalo latte?
I'm good, Peter, thanks.
[director]
Brad, you're up!
[groans]
[grunting]
-Ah!
-[director] Brad? Are you okay?
My back. I threw out my back.
I can't move.
Hey, since you can't
really move right now,
this is probably
a good time to ask,
what's Juliette Lewis
really like?
[straining]
Nice. Talented. Professional.
-A little shrill.
-Yeah, a little shrill.
Yeah, that sounds right.
[groaning, panting]
I don't think I can walk.
We can't push back our schedule
any more.
If Brad's injured,
what are we gonna do?
We'll need a new Chris Christie.
But who could possibly play
that role on such short notice?
I can play that role.
Griffin,
you're not even an actor.
No, but what I am is
a real fat guy.
Brad Pitt was never
the right choice.
This role calls for
real-life fat guy authenticity.
I mean, would Transparent
have been as good
if they just put a guy
in a dress?
Would Neil Patrick Harris
have been as funny
on How I Met Your Mother
if he wasn't
a known heterosexual horndog?
Would Tropic Thunder
have been as authentic
if Robert Downey Jr. wasn't
a dignified Black man?
We're in a jam.
What do you think?
I don't think
we have any other choice.
All right, Griffin,
you got the part.
Awesome! I'm gonna
FaceTime my friends.
They're gonna be
so excited for me.
[FaceTime app ringing]
Oh, boy.
Oh, this-this is sad.
[TV announcer]
We now return to
a steamy business drama
where no one understands
what's happening.
Are you saying we should forge
the EBITDA projections
-for the quarterlies?
-No.
I'm saying
we declare a revenue-miss
while issuing additional shares
based on reduced
capitalization estimates.
Jim, you're in grave danger
of violating
the Glass-Steagall Act.
[Chris]
They haven't shown a bare ass
in three weeks!
Show me your ass, Jim.
[Chris]
And I'm back.
Griffins,
you are looking at the new lead
in the Chris Christie movie.
You? Wh-What happened
to Brad Pitt?
It's what I've been saying
all along, Lois.
He can't do what I do.
He doesn't bring
the fat guy authenticity.
His sweat doesn't smell
like french fries.
He doesn't bring
the sky-high blood pressure
or the jolting sleep apnea.
I have that gift.
That's why.
Peter, this is ridiculous.
You can't play Chris Christie.
You're not even an actor.
Oh, no?
Yes, Lois! Yes! Yes! Oh!
Sound familiar?
-But how do you...?
-Squirt gun full of Ivory.
Sorry, Lunchables, I'm afraid
I've lost my appetite.
Peter, I'm proud of you.
You're actually making
important strides
on behalf of inclusivity
and cultural sensitivity.
Yeah, I'm all for that stuff.
As long as we don't
got to take down
the Confederate statue
in the yard.
That's for history and learning.
Even if they did
come in second place
out of two armies in a war.
-So, how'd we do?
-Second place, baby.
Hey, not bad.
Silver medal. Whoo!
Okay, Peter,
so, in this next scene,
Christie would probably struggle
in the heat and sun
on the George Washington Bridge.
You presume to lecture me
what it's like?
How dare you thinsplain to me?
Talk to me
when your BMI is over 35.
Wow, a real live movie set.
So cool to be here
for the magic.
Yeah, and look,
there's a child star
who's getting an hour of school.
Okay, Billy, now,
what color is this?
-Blue?
-Close enough.
Now get back out there
and be the most distracting
part of any film.
♪ ♪
♪ Making a movie ♪
♪ Not as glamorous as it seems ♪
♪ Standing around ♪
♪ For three hours
just to move a light ♪
♪ Tripping over thick cables
everywhere ♪
♪ Spending all day shooting
one ten-second scene, yeah ♪
♪ Waving flies
off the craft service table ♪
♪ Making a movie ♪
♪ Way more tedious
than it seems ♪
♪ The most important job
is the editor ♪
♪ Staring at a frame
for 18 hours straight ♪
♪ Most of them snap
and go crazy ♪
♪ Even a dumb cartoon like this
takes 18 months ♪
♪ What are we all doing? ♪
[camera shutters clicking]
Oh, Peter,
your big movie premiere.
This is so exciting!
Did Dr. Hartman bring a woman
in a coma as his date?
Hey, guys, big night, huh?
See you in there.
-[crowd clamoring]
-[camera shutters clicking]
Oh, God, here come those
mindless entertainment reporters
who only want to know,
"Who are you wearing?"
-Stewie!
-Stewie.
-Over here, Stewie.
How do you respond to those
who accuse your show
of trafficking in
decades of misogyny,
homophobia and racially
insensitive stereotyping?
Uh... Thom Browne, thank you.
Go, Brian. Go, go, go, go, go.
And here's the star of the film,
Peter Griffin.
What are you wearing tonight,
Peter?
Well, Tom, the shirt is actually
two shirts sewn together.
The jacket is stolen
from a steak house maître d',
and the pants are a towel.
You know, I hear you were
quite the prankster on set.
Well, it wasn't so much pranks
as yelling
and shouting at women.
Yeah, a lot of 'em aren't here
tonight.
They're doing some town hall
meeting with Gloria Allred.
Ah, we'll see what happens.
The after-party's at a Panera
that's still open
to normal customers.
[cheering]
Thank you all for coming.
-[Quagmire] Giggity.
-It was a lot of hard work.
-And thanks to the unnecessarily
long writers' strike,
we were unable to write
a third joke for this speech.
[cheering]
-Hey!
-Ow!
That's your father's movie
up there.
Pay attention, you dope.
♪ ♪
[clamoring on screen]
Repeat after me.
-I's am governor.
-Youse are not.
Big Pussy didn't deserve
to die like that
in The Sopranos.
But he was a freakin' rat!
Congratulations, you are
the governor of New Jersey.
Now let's all root
for the Jets and the Mets
like the idiots we are.
[cheering]
♪ ♪
[thunder crashing]
Lord, please protect us
from this coming hurricane.
It's bad enough you gave me
the same first and last name.
Please don't let me be killed
by a Sandy.
The fellas at the Y would never
let me hear the end of it. Amen.
♪ ♪
[crying]
Oh, Chris, you're dying.
Don't remember me like this.
Remember me stuffed
like a sausage
into that NYPD softball uniform.
♪ But I would walk 500 miles ♪
-[scattered clapping]
-♪ And I would walk 500. ♪
[feigning enthusiasm]
Hey, that was terrific.
[forced]
Oh, what an achievement.
[chuckles awkwardly]
You really did it, buddy.
What are you guys
talking about? I stunk.
I can't act at all.
No...
You were, uh,
very believably fat.
Didn't you notice half the time
I was staring
right into the camera?
They had to use peanut butter
to get me on my mark.
Yeah, but you've done
a great thing
for authenticity
and inclusivity.
I don't even know
what those words mean,
I just like to see your tail wag
when you say 'em.
Peter, you're giving
the marginalized a voice.
How are they marginalized?
The whole country's full
of dumb, fat [bleep].
Now more than ever, we need
authenticity and inclusivity.
No, Brian.
What we need is good actors.
I don't care if they're Black,
white, tall,
short, thin, fat.
Gay, straight--
you forgot those ones.
Look, I-I admit
I thought acting was easy.
And maybe I was blinded
by all the praise I got
from Harvey Weinstein.
Peter, Harvey Weinstein hasn't
had clout for like six years.
Oh, boy. Then I may have done
some things I'll regret.
I don't know, I guess,
as a fat guy, I-I got offended
that Chris Christie wasn't
played by a fat guy.
But turns out it just needed
to be a good actor.
Maybe we should all
spend less time judging
and more time enjoying
what different actors
bring to different roles.
That's the magic
of movies and TV.
[Chris]
And stepson porn.
Chris, you don't have
to join every conversation.
[murmuring]
Okay, look, look, I understand
not everyone will agree
on this issue,
but let's discuss it
in a civilized manner
by making death threats
from our individual homes
to one another on the Internet.
[phone chimes]
Right back at you, buddy.
Well, I'm sorry your movie
didn't go over well, Peter.
Yeah, the money was good,
but I got tired of
all the one-night stands.
-What?
-Huh?
Sorry, my ears have been clogged
since I made out with that guy
from the film crew.
-What?
-Huh?
Well, I got to say, Bri,
it might not have worked out
for Dad,
but I sure got bit
by the acting bug.
Really? You want to be an actor?
Oh, yeah. I'd be great
in Streetcar.
Stella! Stella!
What?!
Is Aidan home?